"幸福大家庭"前情提要...
Previously on "One Big Happy"...
在这里举行的婚礼都是不合法的
None of the weddings that happened here were legal.
本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译制作仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为若因私自散布传播造成法律问题 本字幕组概不负责更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博@大家字幕组
大家字幕组
我的签证一周后就到期了
My visa expires in a week.
如果在那时之前我们不能结婚 我就会被遣送回英格兰
If we're not married by then, I'll be exiled back to England.
哦 我不会让这件事发生的
Well, I'm not gonna let that happen.
大家字幕组
我们再结一次婚好了
We'll just get married again.
我在机场接到了你的父亲
I flew your father in.
- 他不是我父亲 - 我是她的丈夫
- That's not my father. - I'm her husband.
- 什么?  - 我没听错?
- Excuse me? - I'm sorry?
马丁 我没爱过你
I never loved you, Martin.
我只是利用你
I was only using you to get out
来摆脱我当时在家里的尴尬处境
of a bad situation at home.
要不然我怎么会认识你3天
Why else would I marry you
就嫁给你呢？
after only knowing you for three days?
- 让我解释  - 没什么好解释的
- Just let me explain. - There's nothing to explain.
你嫁给了你遇见的第一个混球
You marry the first sucker you meet
来解决你的问题
to solve your problems.
你嫁给我是不是因为你要被驱逐出境呢?
Did you marry me because you were about to be deported?
- 马丁走了   - 卢克也走了
- Martin's gone. - So is Luke.
所以说 现在只有你和我了吧
So, what you're saying is it's just you and me now.
利兹 非常感谢你能让我和你睡
Lizzy, thank you so much for letting me sleep with you.
我醒的时候你就已经在我旁边了
I woke up, and you were next to me,
与其说是让 不如说是你突然袭击
so that's more of an assault than a "Letting."
我只是... 没有卢克
I just... I can't sleep in that bed another night
我晚上睡不着觉
without Luke.
教教我如何面对孤独
Teach me how to be alone.
幸福大家庭
第一季
第六集
翻译
霉霉 Xz 娃娃
鑫鑫 卷卷 David 坑坑
校对
马来福
轴 特效
西子耶
压制
大汪不开森
等等 你之前从来没一个人睡过
So, wait, you've never slept alone before.
这听起来跟你这胸也有自己的重力吸引一样扯
It's like they have their own gravitational pull.
天啊 我好想卢克
God, I miss Luke so much.
我想念他的味道 还有他的抚摸
I miss his smell, I miss his touch,
他亲吻我身体每个部位并和它们说晚安的方式
the way he kisses every single part of my body good night.
他得花一个半小时的时间
It takes him an hour and a half.
但是真的很甜蜜
But it's so sweet.
或许是怀孕的缘故 但是我突然间真的恶心了
It might be the pregnancy, but suddenly I'm nauseous.
但是我主要还是想念他的诗了
But most of all I miss his poetry.
诗? 我非常确定卢克唯一知道的诗就是
Poetry? I'm pretty sure the only poem Luke knows
"啤酒之前喝白酒 忧愁疾病不再有"
is "Beer before liquor never been sicker."
才不是  每晚他都会在纸上写一句话
No. Every night he'd write one word on a note,
然后放在我的枕头上
and then he'd place it on my pillow.
这样在周末 就汇成了一首诗
And then at the end of the week, it'd be a poem.
看
Look.
"心在纠缠
"Hearts intertwined,
甜蜜香唇叫我性欲大发"
soft kisses move my junk."
利兹 如果我俩明天不能结婚
Lizzy, if he and I aren't married by tomorrow,
我就被遣送回国了
I'll be deported...
那样就没人来让他性欲大发了
Then he won't have anyone to move his junk.
普鲁登斯 卢克知道你的签证要到期了
Prudence, Luke knows that your visa is about to expire,
但是他真的对你很失望
but he's really upset with you
而且理由很充分
and for good reason.
它不像你从中间挤牙膏
It's not like you squeezed the toothpaste from the middle
或是用他的剃刀修理你的那个地方
or used his razor on your hoo-ha.
我没那么做过  你瞧?
I'd never do that. See?
我相信你说的
I'll take your word for it.
但是 说真的
But, seriously,
你为什么之前不告诉卢克你结过婚呢？
why didn't you tell Luke that you were married before?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不能怪他不再信任我了
And I can't blame him for not trusting me anymore.
但是难道你没有过一个秘密
But haven't you ever had a secret,
你觉得它让你感到很羞愧吗
like something you were ashamed of,
你并不需要要保守秘密
that you didn't need to keep a secret,
但是你这么做了因为你害怕
but you did because you were afraid
别的人会怎么想你?
of what people might think?
这个倒确实打动我了
That resonates with me, yes.
我保守了一个18年的大秘密
I kept a pretty big secret for 18 years.
好吧 14年
Well, 14.
在幼儿园之前我没想过成为同性恋
I didn't really think about being gay before kindergarten.
哦 等等...珍妮 墨菲
Oh, wait... Jenny Murphy.
所以你懂我啦
So you understand.
哇 也许我们终究并没有那么不同
Wow. Maybe we're not so different after all.
是啊 看看咱俩产生了...共鸣
Yeah, look at us having a... moment.
是啊 看看咱们
Yeah, look at us.
那能不能拜托你帮我跟卢克谈谈?
So will you please talk to Luke for me?
恩 会的 明天一早就谈
Yeah, I will, first thing tomorrow.
谢啦 利兹
Thank you, Lizzy.
这件事多亏你挺我
You've really been my rock through this.
在你那冰冷的外表下
Beneath that icy shell,
是另一层稍微没那么冰冷的外表
is a slightly less cold, additional shell.
共鸣就此结束
And the moment's over.
普鲁登斯真是要了我的命了
Prudence is killing me right now.
她不停地给我发短信
She won't stop texting.
"对不起" 删除 "我爱你" 删除
"I'm sorry." Delete. "I love you." Delete.
这是张照片 保存
That's a photo. Save.
哥们 你这么走来走去暴躁不安有两天了
Dude, you've been pacing and ranting for two days.
我都放任你在墙上砸了个洞
I let you punch a hole in the wall.
你哭的时候我还抱你来着
I held you as you cried
当然这事我绝对守口如瓶
which I will tell no one about.
谢啦 哥们 真是太窝心了
Thank you, man, you've been really tender.
不过你现在应该分散一下注意力
But now you need a distraction.
正好我需要你帮忙
And I need your help.
我遇见个不错的妹子 叫劳瑞 我想给她留个好印象
I met this great girl, Lori, and I wanted to impress her,
所以我也许好像大概跟她说我是个警察
so I might've told her I'm a cop.
我确实跟她说我是个警察来着
I definitely told her I'm a cop.
怪不得你弄了副手铐
That explains the handcuffs.
不 那个我本来就有的
No, those I just have.
不过今晚我和劳瑞会去猎户座酒吧
But Lori and I are going to the Orion tonight
她会带一个朋友一起
and she's bringing a friend,
所以你得选一下 是做凶杀组警探
so you just need to decide if you're a homicide detective
还是坐办公室的
or a desk guy.
看你哭的德性估计你是个坐办公室的
The crying tells me you're a desk guy.
哥们 我才不会去什么冒充条子的四人约会呢
Dude, I'm not going on some fake cop double-date.
那好吧 你做FBI也行
Well, fine, you could be FBI.
我们可以争论一下管辖权
We could argue over jurisdiction.
呃 真是蠢爆了
Well, that's just stupid.
窃听这事我已经折腾了一个月了
I've been working this wire tap for a month.
显然这是我的案子
This is obviously my case.
卢克!
Luke!
你宝贝儿的老妈来啦
Your baby mama's here.
我要去看"学警出更"了 好好学学
I'm gonna go watch "Police Academy," Study up.
你到这来干嘛?
What are you doing here?
给你送西装
Delivering your suit.
你结婚要穿的 也就是今晚
You know, for your wedding that needs to happen tonight.
你是新郎啊 没你怎么结婚
You're the groom, they can't do it without you.
事实上 在本州 还真是可以
Actually, in this state, they can.
如果我不能信任普鲁登斯 我怎么能跟她结婚?
How am I supposed to marry Prudence if I can't trust her?
我是说 不知道下次又是过去的谁谁谁突然冒出来?
I mean, who's gonna show up next from her past?
她那七姐妹之一 其实是她的女儿
One of her seven sisters that's really her daughter,
或是孙女 或是曾孙女吗?
or granddaughter or great-granddaughter?
好吧 普鲁登斯好像也就30吧
Okay, Prudence is like 30.
是么 还是说她其实90了呢?
Is she, or is she like 90?
听着 普鲁登斯没告诉你之前她结过婚
Look, Prudence didn't tell you that she was married before
是因为她感到难为情
because she was ashamed.
就跟她是个没出柜的拉拉差不多
It was almost like she was in the closet.
对你来说每天都是同志荣耀日 是不是啊?
It is always gay pride day with you, isn't it?
而且为毛你突然站在普鲁登斯那边了
And why are you suddenly on Prudence's side.
我是说 把她赶走一直是你梦寐以求的
I mean, you've been dreaming about getting rid of her
打从一开始就是
from the beginning.
才不是那样呢
That's not true.
我听到你往喷泉里扔硬币的时候
I heard you mutter it
咕哝这事来着
as you threw a coin into a fountain.
我认识好几个叫普鲁登斯的
I know a lot of Prudences.
哦 得了吧 利兹 说实话
Oh, come on, Lizzy, be honest.
你讨厌她因为她像扔了一个扳手一样
You resent her for throwing a wrench
搅乱了我们的宝贝计划
into our whole baby plan.
呃 首先 你不应该
Well, first of all, you shouldn't throw
朝小宝宝扔扳手
a wrench around a baby.
就承认了吧 你希望她被驱逐出境
Just admit it, you hope she gets deported.
我很抱歉 但是我不禁认为在某种程度上你是
And I'm sorry, but I can't help but think there's a part of you
故意把她的秘密丈夫请来的!
that flew in her secret husband on purpose!
你在说什么啊?
What are you saying?
我故意把她的秘密丈夫请来的?
That I flew her secret husband in on purpose?
是的 这正是我说的
Yes, that's exactly what I'm saying!
我认为是你破坏了我的婚姻
I think you sabotaged my marriage.
破坏!
Sabotage!
我发誓 我是想把她的老爸接过来
I swear, I thought I was flying in her dad
所以你可以请求得到他的祝福
so that you could ask for his blessing,
多么贴心的举动
which is a very sweet gesture.
闻起来倒像是蓄意的破坏!
Smells like sabotage!
哦 老天!
Oh, my God!
你抽的这是什么啊?
What have you been smoking?
不知道 马库斯 我们抽的是什么?
I don't know, Marcus, what have we been smoking?
那是药用的!
It's medicinal!
大家都冷静冷静!
Everybody calm down!
瞧 我知道你对我很生气
Look, I know that you're angry with me,
但是我也知道你很爱她
but I also know that you love her.
她给我看了一些
She showed me some
你的性感七步诗
of your seven-word sex poems.
精华的部分比如...
Such gems as...
"轻抚 爱揉
"Gentle touches, sweet caresses,
来一发"
we should bang."
改编自真实的故事
Based on a true story.
但是一切都变了 我今晚要去猎户座酒吧
But things have changed, I'm going to the Orion tonight.
所以我会有新的七步诗给你
So I have a new seven-word poem for you.
别回家 别结婚
Not coming home, not getting married.
- 那是六个字 - 再见
- That's six words. - Good day.
那是两个字 现在你完了
That's two, now you're over.
你敢相信卢克指控我尝试
Can you believe Luke accused me of trying to
破坏他们的关系吗?
sabotage the relationship?
太疯狂了 简直有病
That is crazy, that is nutso.
我又不是魔鬼 该死 我是人见人爱的开心果啊
I am not evil, I am a gosh-damn delight.
我是你姐姐 所以我是出于爱才这样说
I'm your sister so I say this with love,
你真的是个邪恶的怪物
but you can be an evil monster.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我去宝拉阿巴杜舞蹈夏令营的那个夏天
You killed my fish the summer I went
你把我的鱼弄死了
to Paula Abdul dance camp.
鱼终有一死
Fish die.
就像我跟你说让爷爷去死吧一样
That's like me saying you let grandpa die.
有时事物就是死了
Sometimes things just die.
对 但是老爸老妈不能支付我们两个都去
Right, but Mom and Dad couldn't afford to send us both
宝拉阿巴拉的舞蹈夏令营 所以他们选择送我去
to Paula Abdul dance camp, so they sent me.
你说你不介意
And you said you were fine
而且会照顾好小鱼罗德尼的
and you would take care of Rodney Dangerfish
但你却一点儿都不尊重它
but gave him no respect.
拜托 我只是有一次忘了喂它
Come on, I forgot to feed him one time.
- 一次? - 几次吧
- One time? - A few times.
- 真的吗? - 好吧 每一次
- Really? - Okay, every single time.
但是本来应该是我在那个舞蹈夏令营的
But it should've been me at that dance camp.
你又不能做这个 还有这个
You can't do this or this.
或者这个
Or this.
是啊 你真是人见人爱的开心果啊
Yeah, you're a gosh-damn delight.
哦 上帝 我杀了你的鱼
Oh, my God, I killed your fish.
或许卢克是对的
And maybe Luke is right.
也许在某种程度上 我是破坏了他和普鲁登斯
Maybe on some level, I sabotaged him and Prudence.
小鱼罗德尼的鬼魂也同意
The ghost of Rodney Dangerfish agrees.
真糟糕
This is terrible.
而且我只有四个小时来搞定这些
And I only have like four hours to fix this,
否则普鲁登斯就要永远消失了
or Prudence is gone for good.
但是如果他都不想和她说话 我能做什么呢?
But what can I do if he won't even talk to her?
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
我疯狂爱上罗伊那会儿
When I get really mad at Roy,
我首先想到的是我一开始为什么
I just remember why I fell in love with him
会爱上他...
in the first place...
你应该知道的
You should know that.
你刚刚给了我灵感
And you just gave me an idea.
我需要做的就是让卢克和普鲁登斯在同一个房间
All I need to do is get Luke and Prudence in the same room
重现他们坠入爱河的场景
and recreate the moment they fell in love.
我记起来了!
I remember!
他让我怀孕了
He got me pregnant.
我是说 警官学校是很严
I mean the police academy was hard.
不过我们有这个
But we had this one guy
能用嘴发出各种音效的家伙
who made fun sound effects with his mouth.
他的警官之路也从此拜拜了
His career kind of dropped off after that.
卢克 跟他们讲讲FBI那档事儿
Luke, tell them about the FBI.
嗯
Mm.
噢 那时有个小气鬼
Oh, there was this one real meany.
这是个执法专业术语
That's a law enforcement term.
他的名字是汉尼拔 莱克特(著名食人杀人狂)
His name was Hannibal Lector.
噢 天哪 他们还以他为原型拍了部电影呢
Oh, my God, they made a movie about him.
你见过他?
You met him?
我只是塔吉特一个小收银员
I'm just a cashier at Target.
就像是个百货商店
It's like a store
在那儿你能买到鞋子
where you can buy shoes
麦片粥 文胸 户外家具
and cereal and bras and outdoor furniture
包装纸 还有...
and wrapping paper and...
我去过塔吉特 嘉琪
I've been to Target, Jackie.
好吧 你们知道么 我兄弟卢克不单单是个FBI特工
Well, you know my man, Luke, is not only an FBI agent,
他还会写淫诗
he also writes sensual poetry.
我就爱诗
I love poetry.
马雅 安琪罗(作家名)妥妥是我的菜啊
Maya Angelou is like... my girl.
给我读一首你的诗吧
Do me one of your poems.
一会儿再读 我得去嘘嘘
Do it later, 'cause I have to pee.
走吧 嘉琪 我们去嘘嘘
Come on, Jackie, let's go pee.
我是得去个嘘嘘了 我们去嘘嘘吧
I totally have to pee. Let's go pee.
拜托 老兄 起来嗨
Come on, man, perk up.
你得让这叽叽喳喳的女孩儿开心
Please just keep the squeaky one entertained.
你不想助我一柱擎天了吗?
Do you not want me to have sex?
讲真的 我是在是不关心
Honestly, I have like zero investment.
我是真没什么兴趣
I'm just not into this.
这是我遇见普鲁登斯的地方
I met Prudence here.
她当时就站在吧台后边
She was standing right behind that bar.
那是我一生中最棒的一个晚上了
Best night of my life.
难道我要放弃这一切了吗?
Am I supposed to just give all that up?
就几个小时而已
Just for like a few hours.
女厕所总是人满为患
The line was too long.
所以我们就在外面嘘嘘了
We peed outside.
利兹 你要带我去哪儿?
Lizzy, where are you taking me?
相信我就好
Just trust me.
等下 这是我跟卢克第一次相遇的酒吧
Wait, this is the bar where Luke and I first met.
我们一见钟情
It was love at first sight.
那是我一生中最棒的一晚了
Best night of my life.
今天咱就来把昨日重现
Well, we're about to deja vu that bitch.
普鲁登斯?
Prudence?
卢克!
Luke!
我不敢相信你在这儿 就像...
I can't believe you're here, this is just like...
那晚我们初次...
The night we first...
我觉得你们俩现在所经历的
I think what you two are experiencing
完全是破坏者的相反版本
is the opposite of sabotage.
我很抱歉 我一直没跟你说...
I'm so sorry that I never told you about...
卢克 我们要走啦
Luke, we're leaving.
你是跟我聊过天的男人里
And you're like the hottest guy
最火辣的了
who's ever talked to me,
你一定要跟我上床
so you're definitely gonna get me to do stuff.
在你大显身手过后你又能写首淫诗
And then you can write a sex poem about that stuff.
- 她是谁? - 她是嘉琪
- Who's she? - She's Jackie.
- 你跟她在一起了 - 没有
- You're with her. - No.
没错 我现在就摸着他的小屁屁呢
Yes, I'm touching his butt right now.
我为你哭了整整两天
I spent two days crying over you.
还给你发了我大咪咪的特写
I sent you glamour shots of my no-no bits.
你却跟别人搞上了
And you're with another girl,
还给她写淫诗?
writing her poems?
她刚刚尿在外面了 那可不是我喜欢的!
She just peed outside, that is not my thing!
现在还不是而已啦
Not yet.
闭嘴 嘉琪!
Shut up, Jackie!
等等 你在塔吉特工作吗?
Wait, do you work at Target?
如果你这么容易就能开始下一段
If it's that easy for you to move on,
那就忘了吧
just forget it.
也忘了我吧!
And forget me!
别 普鲁登斯 等等!
No, Prudence, wait!
- 你没事儿吧? - 当然有!
- Are you okay? - No!
利兹 你到底是在干嘛啊?
Lizzie, what did you do?
修复关系?
I fixed it?
普鲁登斯 你这是要干嘛?
Prudence, what are you doing?
要走
Leaving.
反正他们也会把我驱逐出境的
They're gonna deport me anyway.
也不知道西蒙 考威尔是怎么来去自如的
Yet somehow Simon Cowell walks free.
拜托 别走
Please, don't go.
我在酒吧是给马库斯打掩护的
I was at the bar as Marcus' wingman.
我才不想要嘉琪 那个在塔吉特工作的
I don't want Jackie from Target,
我想要的是普鲁登斯
I want Prudence from
不管你最后是什么工作
whatever job you eventually get.
无所谓啦 别着急嘛
Whatevs, no rush.
对啊 嘉琪根本不是他的菜
Yeah, Jackie's not even his type.
我告诉你啊 在你之前 有过一系列的小贱人
I mean, before you, there was a whole parade of sluts
但她和她们没一点儿一样的地方
that didn't even look anything like her.
利兹 别再努力修复这个了!
Lizzy, stop trying to fix this!
普鲁登斯 我没偷吃
Prudence, I didn't cheat on you.
你一定要相信我
You have to believe me.
好啊 我相信你
Okay, I believe you,
但这也不意味着我应该留在这儿
but it still doesn't mean I should stay.
不过如果你要留下来 你还有一个小时去结婚
But if you do stay, you have an hour to get married,
所以不用着急上火...虽然的确有不少值得上火的事儿
so no presh... Actually, there's a fair amount of presh.
我也很希望我们能和好如初 真的
I want this to work, I really do,
可我就是担心发生了这一切以后
but I'm just afraid that after what happened,
你再也不会相信我了
you're never gonna be able to trust me again.
理由成立 我喜欢你的论证
Valid point. I like where this is going,
非常一针见血
really getting to the core.
我想相信你 但你要现在就告诉我
I wanna trust you, but just tell me now
你过去还有没有其他事情我应该知道?
is there anything else I need to know about your past?
有
Yes.
好吧 听我说
Okay, here goes.
我以前是只丑小鸭
I was an ugly duckling.
我有上包齿和大龅牙
I had an overbite and an underbite.
我遇到过一次电车车祸 这个不是我的真耳朵
I was in a trolley accident, this isn't my real ear.
我还因为从议院泡菜储藏室偷泡菜
And I was once arrested for stealing pickles
而被抓进去过
from the Parliament Pickle Pantry.
那是皮卡迪利广场上的一家泡菜店
It's a pickle shop in Piccadilly Circus.
而且我还说不清楚"蝌搂"(蝌蚪)
And I can't pronounce the word "Tapdole."
蝌搂...哦! 小青蛙
Tapdole... Oh! Baby frog.
哥们儿 她已经全部坦白了
Dude, she just bared her soul.
你怎么说?
What do you say?
我说我爱你
I say I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
那我们就结婚吧
Then let's get married.
哇哦! 哇哦!
Whoa! Whoa!
你们还有58分钟...好么?
You have 58 minutes... okay?
现在别想着搞了!
Stop that now!
你去马库斯那儿拿你的西服
You got to Marcus', grab your suit.
你去穿上你的婚纱
You go put on your wedding dress.
我来负责其它的一切
I'll take care of everything else.
左边的是假的 对吧?
And it's the left one, right?
因为我现在对别的东西都难以直视了
'Cause now I can't look at anything else.
哦 我的个神 你看起来好性感
Oh, my God, you look so hot.
嘉琪 你在这儿干嘛?
Jackie, what are you doing here?
找找你 找到你
Looking for you and finding you,
然后希望能...
and then hopefully...
听着 嘉琪 我很抱歉
Look, Jackie, I'm sorry,
可是我必须在不到一个小时内到婚礼现场
but I have to be at a wedding in less than an hour.
哦 有意思 我可以以你女伴的身份去
Oh, fun, I can go as your date.
不行 杰基 我有女伴...我是新郎
No, Jackie, I have a date... I'm the groom.
听着 嘉琪 如果我误导了你我很抱歉
Look, Jackie, I'm sorry if I misled you in any way.
我只是想帮帮马库斯...
I was only trying to help Marcus...
海托尔警员
Officer Hightower.
- 但我真得走了 - 哦 天啊
- But I gotta go. - Oh, my God.
这种事情总在我身上发生
This always happens to me.
刚刚遇见个好男人
I meet a great guy,
他就要离我而去
and then he leaves me for someone prettier
为了个更漂亮 更聪明 没我这么神经兮兮的人
and smarter and more mentally stable.
嘉琪
Jackie.
别哭了 我最受不了女孩子哭了
Don't cry, I hate it when girls cry.
你知道怎么办我才会高兴点吗?
You know what would cheer me up?
- 你留下来陪我 - 这可绝对不行
- If you stayed. - Oh, I can't.
噢 不小心把你手机扔了
Whoops, I threw your phone.
嘉琪 搞毛啊!
Jackie, no!
猜猜钥匙在哪儿啊?
Guess where the key is?
我说 我搞策划一向很棒的
I mean, I'm a good planner,
但叫我一个小时之内筹备个婚礼出来
but under an hour to throw a wedding together
可差点儿难死姐了
is almost too much to ask.
差一点点
Almost.
现在我们就只差新郎新娘和证婚人了
Now we just need the bride, the groom, and the officiant.
你懂的 就是所有人
So, you know, the wedding.
但是老妹儿啊 你这个已经弄的相当漂亮了啊
But still, Sissy, this is really beautiful.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 亲爱的 - 嗯
- Honey. - Hmm?
你看起来忒开心了吧
You seem really happy.
又出啥事儿了?
What's wrong?
罗伊 我知道我不经常给你提起这事儿
Roy, I know I don't tell you this often enough,
真亏了你当时一炮就把人家搞怀孕了
but good job knocking me up.
啊 宝贝儿 那趟电梯可是哥这辈子坐的最棒的电梯了
Ah, honey, the best elevator ride of my life.
你简直美爆了
You look stunning.
但你就非得穿白的吗?
But white, really?
哇塞 看呐 利兹
Wow. Look at this, Lizzie,
再看看你这身西装穿的
and look at you, rocking that pantsuit
也就只有拉拉或者女政客才能hold的住了
like only a lesbian or female politician could.
咱们就剩20分钟 卢克怎么还没到呢
But we've only got 20 minutes, why isn't Luke here yet?
嘉琪 求你了 赶紧给我解开啊
Jackie, come on, please, uncuff me!
最后再告诉你一次 我是不会
And, for the last time, I am not searching
到你小裤裤里头找钥匙的
your little Jackie for the key.
哦 但人家的下面很想见见你的啊
Oh, but she really wants to meet you.
嘉琪 我离我婚礼开始就剩15分钟了
Jackie, I have 15 minutes to get to my wedding.
哦 我这会儿咋感觉有点晕呢
Oh, I feel a little woozy.
或许真不该再喝九瓶啤酒的
Maybe I shouldn't have had nine beers
忘了我刚吃过一大堆精神病药
when I'm on so many anti-psychotics.
我晕
Whoa.
嘉琪 不要! 坏蛋
Jackie, no! Bad girl!
我愿意
I do.
我滴神啊 卢克到底去哪了
Oh, my God, where is Luke?
我们就剩3分钟了啊
We have three minutes.
他肯定会来的
He's going to show up.
我知道他肯定会来的
I know he's going to show up.
我拿我这个真耳朵担保
I'll bet my real ear on it.
现在不用再给你们隐藏什么了 真叫个轻松啊
It's so nice to have everything out in the open.
肯定是出什么状况了
Something must've happened.
他绝对不会故意错过婚礼的啊
He wouldn't miss this.
我在这儿呢
I'm here!
罗伊
Roy!
你知道我们都在等卢克 瞎喊什么啊
Why would you scream "I'm here," If we're waiting for Luke?
我就想确定你们都知道我还在
I just wanted to make sure you knew where I was.
我刚去拍照了
'Cause I'm taking the pictures.
利兹 如果接下来这2分半还签不了结婚证的话
Lizzy, if this marriage license
我可就真得走人了
isn't signed in 2 1/2 minutes, I'm gone.
好了 老妹儿 你现在可真的没时间了
Okay, Sissy, you're really running out of time.
备用计划是什么?
What's plan "B"?
亲爱的 一般是首选计划行不通了
Honey, that's the plan you use
才会用备用计划的哦
if plan "A" Doesn't work out.
你不要再给我讲话了
You don't get to talk anymore.
就剩最后55秒钟了 成败在此一举了亲
You have 55 seconds, and this is riveting.
你打算怎么办?
What're you gonna do?
对啊 她打算怎么办?
Yeah, what's she gonna do?
对啊 利兹 我该怎么办?
Yeah, Lizzy, what am I gonna do?
你得跟我结婚
You're gonna marry me.
说什么?
What?
我不知道卢克在哪 但他是我最好的朋友
I don't know where Luke is, but he's my best friend,
我知道如果你走了
and I know it would break his heart
他会伤心透顶的 所以...
if you had to leave, so...
我跟你结婚
I'll marry you.
你真要为了我们这么做?
You'd do that for us?
为了我?
For me?
因为一直以来我都以为
Because there have been times when I thought
你可能并不喜欢我
maybe you didn't really like me.
你并没说错
You're not wrong.
我并不总是喜欢你 但是我有点儿慢慢地...
I don't always like you, but I have kind of grown to...
...爱上你了
...love you.
不是吧
No.
利兹 从法律意义上讲我们得保持结婚状态至少...
Lizzy, we'd have to stay legally married for like...
好了 听着 别讲出来
Okay, look, don't talk me out of it.
我只知道我不能眼睁睁地看着另一条鱼死去
All I know is I am not letting another fish die on my watch.
这杯酒敬你 我的小鱼罗德尼
Much respect, Rodney Dangerfish.
为我们证婚吧
Marry us.
呃 好吧
Okay.
众所周知 沃尔特 惠特曼说过...
You know, I think it was Walt Whitman who said that...
那啥 我们只有30秒 跳过惠特曼这段吧
Look, we only have 30 seconds, let's skip the Whitman.
哦 好吧
Ok, sure.
普鲁登斯 班克斯 你愿意娶...
Do you Prudence Banks take...
- 你叫...你叫什么名字? - 利兹 费舍
- What... what's your name? - Lizzy Fisher.
娶利兹 费舍为你的妻子
Take Lizzy Fisher to be your lawfully wedded wife
不论富贵 贫穷 生老病死
for richer or poorer in sickness and in health
直到死亡才能讲你们分开吗?
till death do you part?
我愿意
I do.
我也愿意
I do, too.
由加利福尼亚州赋予的我权利
By the power vested in me, by the state of California,
我现在宣布你们成为妻妻
I now pronounce you wife and wife.
你可以亲吻新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
就这样吧
That's okay.
你们两真是冒牌的天生一对
You guys make a really cute fake couple.
利兹 你可不可以来个微笑 别那样懒散好不呀?
Lizzy, can you just smile and maybe stop slouching?
唠叨 唠叨 唠叨
Nag, nag, nag.
普鲁登斯 我在这儿 咱们结婚吧
Prudence, I'm here, let's get married.
彼以国士待我，我以国士待之，用过免费优质字幕服务，而又有能力的人，有义务将这个免费服务做下去。若有心加入我们 联系QQ群 428872140 更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博 @大家字幕组
你怎么这么久才来?
What took you so long?
这个疯子把她自己和我铐起来了
This looney tune handcuffed herself to me.
我拖着她走了3英里
I had to roll her three miles,
还差点在转弯的时候把她弄丢了
and I lost her on a few corners.
不要问我钥匙在哪儿
And please don't ask where the key is.
哦 你不需要找钥匙
Oh, you don't need a key.
大家字幕组
哇噢 你怎么会...?
Wow, how did you...?
大家字幕组
或许我还需要告诉你一些事儿
Maybe there's a few more things I need to tell you.
好吧 我们来结婚吧
Okay, let's do this.
大家字幕组
呃 亲爱的 太迟了
Uh, darling, um, it's too late.
不 你要被驱逐回国了?
No, you're gonna be deported?
哦 我们的老婆哪儿都不去
Oh, our wife is not going anywhere.
不好意思 "我们的"老婆?
I'm sorry, "Our" Wife?
小伙儿 我妹妹娶了你老婆
Dude, my sister married your wife.
是的 伙计 利兹现在可是你的妈妈了
Yeah, man, I think Lizzy might be your mom now.
利兹和我举行了拉拉结婚 所以我可以一直和你呆在一起了
Lizzy just gay married me so I could stay here with you.
是呀 这就是为什么我们一直艰辛地为同志婚姻做斗争
Yep, that's why we fought so hard.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你为了我和她举行了拉拉结婚?
You gay married her for me?
好吧 这不是"拉拉婚礼" 仅仅是个"婚礼"罢了
Ok, it's not "Gay married", just "Married."
看我 我穿着的鞋子 又不是基佬鞋
I mean, I'm wearing shoes, not gay shoes.
是咩...
Well...
是的 你那双绝壁是基佬鞋 我这个角度看准没错
Yeah, those are totally gay shoes, I've got a really good angle.
她真是你最好的朋友
She really is your best friend.
她也是我最好的朋友
She's kind of mine too.
我爱你
I love you.
- 我也爱你 - 我也爱你哟
- I love you too. - I love you too.
你说啥?
Excuse me?